QUINTON PRICE

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Self-motivated student with a passion for software development and the outdoors. Experience with JavaScript, HTML, React, CSS, git, C++, Python and more. Hoping to gain experience in software development and learn new languages by working with skilled developers.

CONTACT INFORMATION

E-mail: quintonp10@gmail.com

Phone: (253) 310-7627

Website: aprice.net

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/quinton-price

GitHub: github.com/QuintonPrice

SKILLS

- C++
- git
- JavaScript
- React
- Web APIs
- CSS / HTML
- Bootstrap
- Python
- IT Support
- Active Directory / SCCM

EDUCATION

Walla Walla University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

09/2019 - 06/2023

- Taking classes in Web Development, C++, Python, and more
- Dean's List Fall Quarter 2020

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Help Desk Analyst I

Mutual of Enumclaw | 03/2020 - 01/2021, 06/2021 - 09/2021

- Collaborates with members of the IT team, assists with various departmental projects, provides on-call and rotational assignment support.
- Responds to, diagnoses and tracks/documents problems with users. Perform problem recognition, research, and resolution steps.
- Identifies, innovates and suggests new procedures, and/or opportunities to streamline IT Department processing and record-keeping systems and practices.

Website Manager & Trip Leader

Walla Walla University | 02/21 - present

- Manage trip booking website with Flybooks and all relevant processes for Walla Walla University's outdoor association
- Lead outdoor trips with small and large groups doing activities such as mountain biking, cross-country skiing, backpacking, and rock climbing

Help Desk Intern

Mutual of Enumclaw | 06/2019 - 09/2019

- Provides front line support for PC hardware, software, peripheral devices, and network connectivity support for
- Images PCs over network & configures BIOS settings
- Maps network drives, installs advanced programs and works with network
- Experience using BMC Remedyforce Console, Track-IT and Active Directory

NOTABLE PROJECTS

- Android Travel App Android app written in Java that gives users the ability to see destinations near them (with search filters), look up information about locations, use Google Maps, and more.
- Seattle Blog Project React website built from scratch which serves a guide to Seattle and nearby activities. Utilizes React, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, APIs, ES6 and more.
- Personal Portfolio Website which serves as personal portfolio/built with React. Features include blog post components that read JSON info, mobile scaling, and more. Uses Netlify to automatically build / deploy website on each push to the Git repository.